

**Phone:** 0614567633 / 0828425440

**Email:** shondlanihlayiso@gmail.com

**Portfolio:** https://shandlani-in-portfolio.firebaseapp.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/nhlayiso-

shandlani-291630175/

**Location**: Johannesburg, South Africa

ID Number: 9705225867089

# My Technical Skills

- HTML5, CSS, Javascript (Good)
- Bootstrap (Good)
- JQuery (Good)
- Angular 7+ (Good)
- Typescript (Good)
- Ionic Framework (Good)
- SCSS (Good)
- Git (Good)
- Visual Studio Code (Good)
- PHP (Intermediate)
- Java (Intermediate)
- C# (Intermediate)
- ASP.Net Core (MVC) (Intermediate)
- NodeJs (Intermediate)
- Flutter and Dart (Intermediate)
- Adobe After Effects (Intermediate)
- Python (Entry-Level)
- Cordova (Intermediatte)

# References

- Sinomuzi Mathebula (CE0 @ MK Innovations)
  - 078 596 7635 / 013 065 0396
- Mpumelelo Hlatswayo (Co-Founder @ Yellow Bin Sa)
  - 078 770 1274 / 068 311 0394 / info@yellowbinsa.com
- 3. Karabo (Front End Developer (Former)@ Mkholo Projects)
  - 067 011 4331

# **Image Nhlayiso Shandlani**

Front End Developer

#### **Summary**

I am a passionate and hardworking front end developer with a solid 3years of experience in the field. I have worked with some of the leading and preferred APis, libraries and tech stacks that developers use during that time. I am always learning new skills and upskilling those that I am familiar with to keep up with trends in the industry.

### **Experience**

#### 1. Front End Developer

@ MK Innovations (Jan 2022 - Dec 2022)

Reason for leaving: Contract Ended

- Developing the front for web, android and ios platforms. Optimizing the apps for each platform using a single tech stack
- Using data to make the applications more interactive and responsive
- Main Tools NodeJs, Angular, Typescript, SCSS, Firebase, HERE Maps, HTML5

#### 2. Front End Developer (Freelance)

@ Yellow Bin SA (Nov 2021 – Jan 2022)

Reason for leaving: **Development, testing & deployment completed** 

- Developed the front for a trash collection site
- Main Tools NodeJs, Angular, Typescript, SCSS, Firebase HTML5
- Web <a href="https://yellowbinsa.com">https://yellowbinsa.com</a>, Playstore <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=za.co.yellowbin">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=za.co.yellowbin</a>

#### 3. Front End Developer (Freelance)

@ Onkas Hub (March 2021 – July 2021)

Reason for leaving: Development, testing & deployment completed

- Developed the front for an online accessory store
- Tools NodeJs, Angular, Typescript, SCSS, Firebase, HTML5
- Web www.oahub.co.za

#### 4. Front End Developer (Freelance)

@ Thuma Mina Delivery (Oct 2020 – Dec 2020)

Reason for leaving: Development, testing & deployment completed

- Developed the front end for a food delivery brand in Nelspruit
- Main Tools NodeJs, Angular, Typescript, SCSS, Firebase, HTML5
- Web <u>www.2mamina.co.za</u>

#### 5. Front End Web Developer

@ Mkholo Projects (July 2019 – Jun 2020)

Reason for leaving: Contract Ended

- Responsible for building and developing the front end for web applications
- Optimizing the apps for mobile and desktop browsers
- Maintaing applications on the server and also deploying them
- Main Tools HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap, PHP

# **Education**

# 1. National Diploma : Information Technology (Multimedia)

From: Tshwane University of Technology (Pretoria, South Africa)

Date Completed: 2019

# 2. Introduction To Machine Learning (Data Science)

From: Kaggle Data Science Community (Online)

Date Completed: 2022

# 3. Grade 12 (Matric)

From: Topaz Secondary School (Pretoria, South Africa)

Date Completed: 2015